export const chapter = "Chapter - 10: Verbs";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
        {
          question: "What is a Verb primarily responsible for expressing?",
          optionA: "Emotion",
          optionB: "Existence",
          optionC: "Identity",
          correctAnswer: "Existence",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which of the following sentences demonstrates a Verb showing existence?",
          optionA: "The thief stole a necklace.",
          optionB: "We were fast friends.",
          optionC: "Always speak the truth.",
          correctAnswer: "We were fast friends.",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which category do Verbs like 'is dancing' and 'will rise' fall into according to the text?",
          optionA: "Primary Verbs",
          optionB: "Helping Verbs",
          optionC: "Action Verbs",
          correctAnswer: "Helping Verbs",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What is the role of words like 'is,' 'was,' 'were,' and 'will' in sentences with multiple verbs?",
          optionA: "Main Verbs",
          optionB: "Action Verbs",
          optionC: "Helping Verbs",
          correctAnswer: "Helping Verbs",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In the sentence 'The girls will be dancing on the stage,' what are 'will be' and 'dancing'?",
          optionA: "Main Verbs",
          optionB: "Helping Verbs and Main Verbs",
          optionC: "Action Verbs",
          correctAnswer: "Helping Verbs and Main Verbs",
        },
        {
          question: "What is the purpose of Tense in verbs?",
          optionA: "Expressing existence",
          optionB: "Indicating time",
          optionC: "Showing emotion",
          correctAnswer: "Indicating time",
        },
        {
          question:
            "When a sentence is in the Present Tense, what does it signify?",
          optionA: "Future events",
          optionB: "Past events",
          optionC: "Current events",
          correctAnswer: "Current events",
        },
        {
          question: "Which sentence represents the Past Tense?",
          optionA: "The girl is in the bed.",
          optionB: "We played together with a ball.",
          optionC: "He has written a letter.",
          correctAnswer: "We played together with a ball.",
        },
        {
          question: "What does the Future Tense indicate?",
          optionA: "Past events",
          optionB: "Current events",
          optionC: "Future events",
          correctAnswer: "Future events",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In the sentence 'You will have spoken the truth,' which part represents the Future Tense?",
          optionA: "You will",
          optionB: "Have spoken",
          optionC: "The truth",
          correctAnswer: "You will",
        },
      ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blank with correct option:",
    questions: [
        {
          question:
            "Some Verbs show existence; for example:\nI am a __________.\n",
          optionA: "person",
          optionB: "girl",
          optionC: "boy",
          correctAnswer: "boy",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Some Verbs show action. They are doing words; for example:\nAlways speak __________ truth.\n",
          optionA: "a",
          optionB: "the",
          optionC: "an",
          correctAnswer: "the",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Some Verbs can be made up of more than one word; for example:\nAnjali is dancing __________ the room.\n",
          optionA: "at",
          optionB: "on",
          optionC: "in",
          correctAnswer: "in",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In these sentences, the Verbs have two words: is dancing, was running, were playing, and __________ respectively.\n",
          optionA: "jump",
          optionB: "climb",
          optionC: "rise",
          correctAnswer: "rise",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The words: is, was, were, and will are helping the Main Verbs to express their meanings respectively. So, they are called __________ Verbs.\n",
          optionA: "Primary",
          optionB: "Action",
          optionC: "Helping",
          correctAnswer: "Helping",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Some Verbs can have even three or four words; for example:\nThe girls will be dancing on __________ stage.\n",
          optionA: "a",
          optionB: "an",
          optionC: "the",
          correctAnswer: "the",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In these sentences, the Helping Verbs are will be and shall have been, and the Main Verbs are dancing and playing.\nThe Helping Verbs are used to assist the Main Verbs in expressing their meanings. So, they are called __________ Verbs.\n",
          optionA: "Primary",
          optionB: "Action",
          optionC: "Helping",
          correctAnswer: "Helping",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The Verbs can be used in different times. They can show the present, past, or future time. These times are called __________.\n",
          optionA: "Clauses",
          optionB: "Phrases",
          optionC: "Tenses",
          correctAnswer: "Tenses",
        },
        {
          question:
            "When something happens now, it is in the Present Tense; for example:\nThe girl is in __________ bed.\n",
          optionA: "a",
          optionB: "an",
          optionC: "the",
          correctAnswer: "the",
        },
        {
          question:
            "When something happened in the past, it is in the Past Tense; for example:\nHe was in __________ jail.\n",
          optionA: "an",
          optionB: "the",
          optionC: "a",
          correctAnswer: "the",
        },
      ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
        {
          question:
            "The Verbs in the sentences 'Anjali is dancing in the room' and 'We were playing hockey yesterday' have two words each.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Definite Articles ('The') are used with names of political parties, organizations, nationalities, races, etc., such as 'the Indian National Congress,' 'the United Nations,' 'the Chinese,' etc.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question: "Indefinite Articles (A, An) are used with specific nouns.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In the sentence 'She is the most beautiful girl in the colony,' 'the' is used before the superlative degree of Adjectives.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The words 'European,' 'unicorn,' and 'uniform' begin with a vowel letter but with a consonant sound.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The word 'hour' begins with 'h' (Consonant letter) but with a vowel sound.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Use of 'An': 'An' is used with words that begin with a consonant sound.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Definite Article ('The') is used with names of natural things such as the sun, the earth, the stars, the moon, the cloud, the South, etc.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The word 'A' is always used before a word starting with a consonant sound.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Use of 'A': 'A' is used with words that begin with a vowel sound.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
      ],
  };
}

export var activityData;
